

RIDHA RIZQIYANTY ROBINA

081383594832 | ridharobina@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ridha-robina-086659224 | https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Cwy7cFDcujWRnw5eN5Dx35cB88MK_hO5/view?usp=drive_link

JL CIDAHU TANGKIL KP.CIPANAS

The creative industry is an interesting department that I reach, that's why I am choosing to be a student at Manajemen of Media Production in Communication Science. I got many experiences since senior high school in making copywriting, storyboarding in short movies, being a designer and social media controller, being a talent, and joining an agency for a content creator. and I love it because my passion is there. a value that I got is can be improving myself to be professional and creative.

Work Experiences

Syamsul Falah Kindergarten School - Cidahu, Sukabumi, West

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Java, Indonesia

teacher assistant

a preschool educational approach based on playing, singing, practical activities such as drawing, and social interaction

· Teaching private for student at kindergarten school

Junior High School 1 Cidahu - Cidahu, Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia

Mar 2020 - Dec 2020

Teacher of Scout Extrakulikuler

Leading and teaching an ekstrakulikuler at Senior High School 1 Cidahu

- · coordinating for preparation scout competition student
- · leading and teaching manner of scout

Teman Jajan Cafe & Catering - Cidahu, Sukabumi, West Java,

Dec 2020 - Present

Indonesia

Social Media Manager

as Content creator focusing on fotographer, videographer advertising and admin of social media specialist https://www.instagram.com/temanjajankuy/

- · Fotographer product
- · videographer advertising
- · designer of social media

Thrifthyuk26 - Cidahu, Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia

Mar 2023 - Present

Social Media Specialist

a small bisnis that i built with my sister which is focusing on thrfiting olshop in media social

https://www.instagram.com/thriftyuk26/

Paragon Corp - Pesanggrahan, Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Content & Copy Writer

Paragon is an Indonesia beauty company with the purpose of creating a greater good for the society through innovation.

- As admin social media @beyondlyofficiall @Paragonbusinesspartner @womanergy
- · Create a content brief, content plan, script writer
- · photographer, videographer, editor event of beyondly

Bank Indonesia - Tasikmalaya, West Java, Indonesia

May 2024 - Present

Intern of UPPUKIS dan UDSK

A company that manages three areas, namely Monetary, Payment Systems and Financial System Stability

- · Internal of public relations corporate
- Building communication between corporate and UMKM

Education Level

Universitas Padjadjaran ⊙ - sumedang, west java, Indonesia

Jul 2021 - Jun 2024

Diploma in in Manajemen of Media Production, 3.70/4.00

- Awardee of the most outstanding student category Diploma at Faculty of communication sciences 2023
- First winner of Earthview Cinema competition UIN Sunan Kalijaga 'Party of Public Relations'

Organisational and Committee Experience

Head of Social and Environment Departement

· Controlling every project based on envinronment and social

BEM Kema Unpad - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Staff of Environment Departement

- as documenter of social and environment project
- scriptwriter and content creator of environment department
- contributing on social and environment project

Jabar Bergerak Zilenial Kab.Sukabumi - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Sep 2021 - Dec 2022

Mar 2022 - Present

Head of MSDM Departement

An organization which is a part of Jabar Bergerak focusing on social project in Sukabumi Village

- · controlling project every department
- · improving everyone for being productive staff
- · doing some project which is related by department

ST22 - Jakarta, Indonesia

Jul 2022 - Present

- Content creator of Community Member
- · Content creator
- Sharing information of some product based on video review

HIMA MPM of Padjadjaran University - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

Staff Of Internal Relation

· as host of hubin talks

Jatinangor Social Festival - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Head of Liailison office

- · Lialising and accompanying the organizers with external participants
- as public relation with Sanggar and Stake holder arround Jatinangor

Dialog Candradimuka Faculty of Communication Science - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Staff of Event

- Host of Event
- · Coodinating with all event staff
- · Sequence of events from start to finish
- · Help other staff to launch activities

"Kampung Lingkungan" BEM KEMA Unpad - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Head of Design, Visual and Publication division

- · Controlling social media
- · Responsibility of media production and media publication

Unpad Award - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Staff of Menejement Information

- Content Creator of Social media Unpad award
- Talent of trailer awarding night

Padjadjaran Educational Festival - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Staff of Decoration

- · Consepting every visual event
- · Drawing and decorate location of event

Fikom Award - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

Staff of Nomination

- · Accounting score project every departement at BEM KEMA Fikom Unpad
- · Decide a winner every nomination

World Environment Festival by BEM KEMA Unpad - Sumedang, West Java, Indonesia

- Present

- Staff of media partner
- · Controlling of media partner
- · looking for a media partner
- Talk force for external relation

Liaison Officer

National journalism competition held in several cities, which carries the main theme of concern for the conservation of wild animals

- Controlling of grand opening event Wildlife Journalism Competition
- · As liaison officer of registered

Achievement, Skill

- Achievements (2021): Best Female Fashion at Pesta Rakyat Komunikasi
- Achievements (2021): Winner of One Minute Speak Up with BKI Fikom Unpad
- Achievements (2020): Brand Ambassador of @ief.educator
- Achievements (2018): Awardee Scholarsip Senior High School class of XI
- Projects (2021): Built a "Melukis Indonesia" Project
- Projects (2021): As Host, Moderator, and discussion responder at webinar series with Mrs. Meutya Hafidz and Mr. Addies MS
- Soft Skills (2022): MC of Orientation Student at Fikom Unpad
- Soft Skills (2022): MC of closing orientation djatinangor jurnalist
- Soft Skills (2022): Host of Hubin talks HIMA MPM Unpad on YouTube
- Soft Skills (2022): Host of Live Instagram World Environment Festival with BEM Kema Unpad " Ketahanan Pangan di Indonesia "
- Soft Skills (2022): as talent of trailer awarding night Unpad Award
- Soft Skills (2023): Host of Grand Launching Hima MPM Fikom Unpad
- Interpersonal Skills: Communication, Public Speaking, Leadership, Team work, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving.
- **Technical Skills**: Creative, Content Creator, Content Writing, Human Resources, Social Media Managing, Event Managing, Decoration, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Exel, Canva, Audiovisual, Editor App
- Achievements (2023): Mawapres Diploma Fikom Unpad
- Projects (2023): Short movie project as art director and talent acquisition